[
    {
        "question": "AngularJS is a ____",
        "answer": "Answer: B) AngularJS is a JavaScript framework.",
        "options": [
            "Java framework",
            "JavaScript framework",
            "HTML framework",
            "SQL framework"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "AngularJS is perfect for?",
        "answer": "Answer: D) AngularJS is perfect for SPAs.",
        "options": [
            "MPAs",
            "DPAs",
            "CPAs",
            "SPAs"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Among the following, on which architectural pattern is AngularJS based?",
        "answer": "Answer: C) AngularJS is based on an MVVM architecture pattern.",
        "options": [
            "Decorator pattern",
            "Observer pattern",
            "MVVM architecture pattern",
            "MVC architecture pattern"
        ]
    },
    null,
    {
        "question": "Choose the correct syntax for writing AngularJS expression.",
        "answer": "Answer: B) {{expressions}} is the correct syntax.",
        "options": [
            "[expression]",
            "{{expressions}}",
            "{{{expressions}}}",
            "{expressions}"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the reactor which is used to bind the application data to the HTML view in AngularJS.",
        "answer": "Answer: A) ng-bind directive is used to bind the application data to the HTML view in AngularJS.",
        "options": [
            "ng-bind directive",
            "ng-model directive",
            "ng-init directive",
            "ng-app directive"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the correct statement about the lowercase filter.",
        "answer": "Answer: B) Lowercase filter converts a text to lowercase text is correct.",
        "options": [
            "it is a function that takes text as input",
            "the lowercase filter converts a text to lowercase text",
            "both a and b",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the advantage of Angular JS among the following.",
        "answer": "Answer: D) All of the above advantages of Angular JS",
        "options": [
            "it provides reusable components",
            "it uses dependency injection and makes use of separation of concerns",
            "it is unit-testable",
            "all of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The functionality of angular controllers in the application is",
        "answer": "Answer: B) Angular controllers are used for controlling the data",
        "options": [
            "an angular controller is used for displaying the data",
            "an angular controller is used for controlling the data",
            "both a and b",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The syntax used to create a module in AngularJS is:",
        "answer": "Answer: A) module(“app”,[]) is the correct syntax used to create a module in AngularJS",
        "options": [
            "module(“app”,[])",
            "var myModule=angular.module();",
            "var myModule = new Module();",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the incorrect AngularJS filter.",
        "answer": "Answer: B) email is not an AngularJS filter.",
        "options": [
            "orderby",
            "email",
            "currency",
            "lowercase"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the father of AngularJS?",
        "answer": "Answer: A) Misko Hevery is the father of AngularJS.",
        "options": [
            "Misko Hevery",
            "Brad Green",
            "Mike Adams",
            "Adam a bronze"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the directive which is used to find the values of HTML controls to application data.",
        "answer": "Answer: A) ng-model is used to find the values of HTML controls to application data.",
        "options": [
            "ng-model",
            "ng-init",
            "ng-app",
            "ng-hide"
        ]
    },
    null,
    {
        "question": "Module created by using AngularJS function is known as",
        "answer": "Answer: B) Module created by using AngularJS function is known as a module().",
        "options": [
            "module()",
            "mod()",
            "Angular module()",
            "mdl()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The total $RootScope an AngularJS application can have is?",
        "answer": "Answer:  B) Total $RootScope an AngularJS application can have is 1.",
        "options": [
            "0",
            "1",
            "2",
            "3"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following components is the one which can be injected as a dependency in Angular JS?",
        "answer": "Answer: C) Application module can be injected as a dependency in AngularJS.",
        "options": [
            "Factory",
            "Constant",
            "Application module",
            "Value"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the correct definition of deep thinking in AngularJS",
        "answer": "Answer: B) Deep linking allows you to encode the state of an application in the URL so that it can be bookmarked.",
        "options": [
            "Deep linking refers to Linking various views to the main page",
            "Deep linking allows you to encode the state of an application in the URL so that it can be bookmarked",
            "Deep linking is an SEO based technique",
            "all of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Among the following which can be used to write AngularJS directives",
        "answer": "Answer: D) All of the above can be used to write the AngularJS directives.",
        "options": [
            "Attribute",
            "class name",
            "Tag",
            "all of the above"
        ]
    },
    null,
    null,
    {
        "question": "AOT stands for ________",
        "answer": "Answer: B) AOT stands for Ahead of Time compilation.",
        "options": [
            "Angular Object Templates",
            "Ahead of Time compilation",
            "Both a and b",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the incorrect hook application lifecycle.",
        "answer": "Answer: B)ngViewStart is not a hook application lifecycle.",
        "options": [
            "noOnInit",
            "ngViewStart",
            "ngOnChanges",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The router is a part of which of the following given models?",
        "answer": "Answer: A) Router is a part of @angular/router. of",
        "options": [
            "@angular/router",
            "@angular/core",
            "Both a and b",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What can RxJS be used for?",
        "answer": "Answer: C) RxJS can be used for both Server-side and browser.",
        "options": [
            "Server-side",
            "Browser",
            "Both a and b",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which decorator is used for configuring model class",
        "answer": "Answer: B)@NgModule is used for configuring the model class.",
        "options": [
            "@NgApp",
            "@NgModule",
            "Both a and b are correct",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the functionality of.angular-cli.json  among the following.",
        "answer": "Answer: A) .angular-cli.json is used to configure the angular 2 projects.",
        "options": [
            "used to configure angular 2 project",
            "used to install required  project packages",
            "used to link external files",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Among the following choose the one which is responsible for the startup of the angular 2 projects.",
        "answer": "Answer: B) main.ts is Responsible for the startup of the angular 2 project",
        "options": [
            "app.ts",
            "main.ts",
            "index.js",
            "angular.cli.json"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How is interpolation in angular 2 done?",
        "answer": "Answer: B )Using {{}} interpolation is done in angular 2.",
        "options": [
            "{{{}}}",
            "{{}}",
            "{{|var}}",
            "!!!!"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the filter which is used to convert the input to all uppercase",
        "answer": "Answer: C) uppercase Is used to convert the input to uppercase.",
        "options": [
            "toUpper",
            "upper",
            "uppercase",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "To detect changes in the angular 2 project which of the following is used?",
        "answer": "Answer: A) zone.js is used to detect changes in the angular 2 project.",
        "options": [
            "zone.js",
            "scope.js",
            "zones.js",
            "zone$,js"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a feature of angular 2?",
        "answer": "Answer: B) Multithread is not a feature of angular 2",
        "options": [
            "Typescript",
            "multi-thread",
            "Components",
            "services"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is used to retrieve a list of items from a server’s URL?",
        "answer": "Answer: D) To retrieve a list of items from a server’s URL, create a URL transaction.",
        "options": [
            "Using the http get method",
            "using an HTTP package",
            "create a get SQL  statement",
            "create a URL transaction"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the correct definition of routerOutlet.",
        "answer": "Answer: B) routerOutlet is a directive defined in the HTML indicating where the route’s view should display.",
        "options": [
            "A decorator defines the template to display when a route is activated",
            "a directive defined in the HTML indicating where the route’s view should display",
            "A directive defined in the HTML identifying the route to activate",
            "A property of component class used to activate a route"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following can be used as a prefix for directive?",
        "answer": "Answer: C) Both A and B can be used as a prefix for the directive.",
        "options": [
            "ng-",
            "data-",
            "Both a and b",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the correct definition of the view in MVC.",
        "answer": "Answer: A) View is responsible for displaying all or a portion of data to the user.",
        "options": [
            "View is responsible for displaying all or a portion of data to the user",
            "View is responsible to act and process the data",
            "View represents the database view",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "On which of the types of components can a custom derivative be created?",
        "answer": "Answer: D) All of the above types of components can be used to create a custom derivative.",
        "options": [
            "Attribute",
            "element directives",
            "CSS",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    null,
    null,
    {
        "question": "Among the following which is not built-in a pipe in angular?",
        "answer": "Answer: B) DataPipe Is not built-in a pipe in angular.",
        "options": [
            "CurrencyPipe",
            "DataPipe",
            "PercentPipe",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the valid AngularJS expression.",
        "answer": "Answer: C) {{2+2}} is correct expression.",
        "options": [
            "{(2+2)}",
            "{2+2}",
            "{{2+2}}",
            "((2+2))"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which decorator is used to make a class a service?",
        "answer": "Answer: A) Injectable is used to make a class service.",
        "options": [
            "Injectable",
            "Component",
            "Server",
            "injector"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the functionality of the @output decorator?",
        "answer": "Answer: A) @output is used to share data from child component to parent.",
        "options": [
            "Add OptionShare data from child component to parent1",
            "use a service",
            "use event  binding",
            "share data from the parent component to a child"
        ]
    },
    null,
    {
        "question": "Which function is used to import RouterModule in a feature module?",
        "answer": "Answer: D) forChild() is used to import RouterModule in a feature module.",
        "options": [
            "forRoot()",
            "forModule()",
            "forFeature()",
            "forChild()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Most used CSS frameworks are ________",
        "answer": "Answer: C) Most used CSS frameworks are bootstrap.",
        "options": [
            "SASS",
            "Semantic UI",
            "Bootstrap",
            "Foundation"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "AngularJS was developed by which company?",
        "answer": "Answer: B) AngularJS was developed by Google.",
        "options": [
            "Facebook",
            "Google",
            "Angular",
            "Netflix"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the functionality of the @input decorator",
        "answer": "Answer: D) @input is used to share data from the parent component to the child.",
        "options": [
            "Share data from child component to parent",
            "use a service",
            "use event  binding",
            "share data from parent component to child"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the definition of transpilers.",
        "answer": "Answer: C) Transpiler are the source to source compiler.",
        "options": [
            "Converts source to the library",
            "Convert source to source and then to the library",
            "source to source compiler",
            "all of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Angular CLI stands for ____________",
        "answer": "Answer: C) Angular CLI stands for Angular command-line interface.",
        "options": [
            "Angular command-line interceptor",
            "Angular command line",
            "Angular command-line interface",
            "Angular command-line user interfaces"
        ]
    }
]